Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - J
        - Just-Ice - Girls n guns, 1993; SR-19579; Just-Ice (Box 315)
        - Just-Ice - Keep it real; Bad boy back in town, 1996; SR-19580; Just-Ice (Box 315)
          In same jacket as # SR-19581. 2 copies.
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # S-33520
          In-A-Minute Records
          Emeryville, California
        - Just-Ice - Keep it real; Bad boy back in town, 1996; SR-19581; Just-Ice (Box 315)
          In same jacket as # SR-19580. 2 copies.
        - Just-Ice - Keep it real; Bad boy back in town, 1996; SR-19582; Just-Ice (Box 315)
        - Just-Ice - The desolate one, 1989; SR-19583; Just-Ice (Box 315)
          Catalog # LPRE-82010; A-side Matrix # LPRE 82010-Y
        - Just-Ice - Put that record back on; LaToya, 1986; SR-19584; Just-Ice (Box 316)
          In same jacket as # SR-19585. 2 copies.
          Catalog # FRE-003; A-side Matrix # FRE-003-X
        - Just-Ice - Put that record back on; LaToya, 1986; SR-19585; Just-Ice (Box 316)
          In same jacket as # SR-19584. 2 copies.
        - Just Jack - Paradise (lost & found), 2002; SR-19586; Just Jack (Box 316)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # RGRCD1-12A
          RG Records
        - Just Us - Voice of the haunted, 1990; SR-19587; Just Us (Box 316)
          Catalog # CENT 100-1; A-side Matrix # CENT 100-1
          Central Station
          Sydney, Australia
        - Justice System - Summer in the city, 1994; SR-19588; Justice System (Box 316)
          Catalog # MCA8P 3069; A-side Matrix # MCA-11988-MD2
        - Justice System - Summer in the city, 1994; SR-19589; Justice System (Box 316)
        - Justice System - Summer in the city, 1994; SR-19590; Justice System (Box 316)
        - Justice System - Rooftop soundcheck (disc one), 1994; SR-19591; Justice System (Box 316)
          In same jacket as # SR-19592. Double album.
          Catalog # MCA2-11118; A-side Matrix # MCA-12017-1
        - Justice System - Rooftop soundcheck (disc two), 1994; SR-19592; Justice System (Box 316)
          In same jacket as # SR-19591. Double album.
          Catalog # MCA2-11118; A-side Matrix # MCA-12019-1
        - Justice System - Summer in the city, 1994; SR-19593; Justice System (Box 316)
          Catalog # MCA12 54869; A-side Matrix # MCA-11987-MD2
        - Justice System - Dedication to Bambaataa, 1994; SR-19594; Justice System (Box 316)
          Catalog # MCA8P 3228; A-side Matrix # MCA 12142-1
        - Justice System - Dedication to Bambaataa, 1994; SR-19595; Justice System (Box 316)
        - Justice System - Dedication to Bambaataa, 1995; SR-19596; Justice System (Box 316)
          Catalog # MCA12 54997; A-side Matrix # MCA-12143-1
        - Justin - Think (about it), 1982; SR-19597; Justin (Box 316)
          In same jacket as # SR-19598. 2 copies.
          Catalog # TEES 12-11; A-side Matrix # TEES-12-11-A-RE
          Stiff Records
        - Justin - Think (about it), 1982; SR-19598; Justin (Box 316)
          In same jacket as # SR-19597. 2 copies.
        - Juvenile - I got that fire, 2000; SR-19599; Juvenile (Box 316)
          In same jacket as # SR-19600. 2 copies.
          Catalog # UNIR-20203-1; A-side Matrix # UNIR-20203-1A
        - Juvenile - I got that fire, 2000; SR-19600; Juvenile (Box 316)
          In same jacket as # SR-19599. 2 copies.
        - Juvenile - U understand, 1999; SR-19601; Juvenile (Box 316)
          Catalog # U8P 1669; A-side Matrix # U8P-1669-A
        - Juvenile - Back that azz up, 1999; SR-19602; Juvenile (Box 316)
          In same jacket as # SR-19603. 2 copies.
          Catalog # U8P 1545; A-side Matrix # U8P-1545-A
        - Juvenile - Back that azz up, 1999; SR-19603; Juvenile (Box 316)
          In same jacket as # SR-19602. 2 copies.
        - Juvenile - U understand, 1999; SR-19604; Juvenile (Box 316)
        - Juvenile - Follow me now; Back that azz up, 1999; SR-19605; Juvenile (Box 316)
          Catalog # U8P 1483; A-side Matrix # U8P-1483-A
        - Juvenile - 400 degreez, 1999; SR-19606; Juvenile (Box 316)
          Catalog # U8P 1449; A-side Matrix # U8P-1449-A
        - Juvenile - Ha!, 1998; SR-19607; Juvenile (Box 316)
          Catalog # U8P 1326; A-side Matrix # U8P-1326-A
        - Juvenile - Juve the great, 2003; SR-19608; Juvenile (Box 316)
          Catalog # B0001718-01; A-side Matrix # B0001718-01A
        - Juvenile - Way I be leanin'; What's happenin' (fresh remix), 2006; SR-19609; Juvenile (Box 316)
          Catalog # PR 302227; A-side Matrix # ST PR 302227 A1
        - Juvenile - Juve the great, 2003; SR-19610; Juvenile (Box 316)
        - Juvenile - Reality check (disc one), 2006; SR-19611; Juvenile (Box 316)
          In same jacket as # SR-19612. Double album.
          Catalog # 83790-1; A-side Matrix # ST-A-83790-A-1-RE1
        - Juvenile - Reality check (disc two), 2006; SR-19612; Juvenile (Box 316)
          In same jacket as # SR-19611. Double album.
          Catalog # 83790-1; A-side Matrix # ST-A-83790-C-1-RE1
        - Juvenile - Sets go up, 2005; SR-19613; Juvenile (Box 316)
          Catalog # PR 301749; A-side Matrix # ST-BB-301749-A-1
        - Juvenile - Back that azz up, 1999; SR-19614; Juvenile (Box 316)
        - Juvenile - I got that fire, 2000; SR-19615; Juvenile (Box 316)
        - Juvenile - From her mama; Set it off, 2001; SR-19616; Juvenile (Box 316)
          Catalog # 422 860 962-1; A-side Matrix # 422-860-962-1A
        - Juvenile - Set it off, 2001; SR-19617; Juvenile (Box 316)
          Catalog # UNIR 20533-1; A-side Matrix # UNIR-20533-1-A
        - Juvenile - Follow me now; Back that azz up, 1999; SR-19618; Juvenile (Box 316)
        - Juvet, Patrick - I love America, 1978; SR-19619; Juvet, Patrick (Box 316)
          Catalog # NBD 20134; A-side Matrix # NBD-20134-AS
        - Juvet, Patrick - Lady night; Swiss kiss, 1979; SR-19620; Juvet, Patrick (Box 316)
          Catalog # NBD 20160; A-side Matrix # NBD-20160-AS-2CP
        - Juzt 2 Brothers - Las mujeres estan (ladies are hot!), 1996; SR-19621; Juzt 2 Brothers; Los Compadres; Wepaman (Box 316)
          Catalog # CR-380; A-side Matrix # CR-380-A
          Cutting Records
        - Juzt 2 Brothers - La bandera "the flag", 1997; SR-19622; Juzt 2 Brothers (Box 316)
          Catalog # CR-417; A-side Matrix # CR417A
        - JVC Force - Big trax; 6 feet back on the map, 1992; SR-19623; JVC Force (Box 316)
          Catalog # DMD 1775; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-61477-61478-5
        - Jackson 5 - Moving violation, 1975; SR-30764; Jackson 5 (Box 316)
          Catalog # M6-829S1; A-side Matrix # M6-829S1-E5 RS-7570-1 1-03A
        - Daniel Jackson Explosion - Cinderella (Queen of the dance); Hymn for Africa, 1977; SR-30765; Daniel Jackson Explosion (Box 316)
        - Jackson, Freddie - Sinmix volume 7, 1994; SR-30766; Jackson, Freddie; Savage, Chantay; Warren, Christian; E-Smoove (Box 316)
          Catalog # SIN-1680-A; A-side Matrix # SIN-1680-A
          Sinmix Vinyl
        - Jackson, Michael - Got to be there, 1972; SR-30767; Jackson, Michael (Box 316)
          Catalog # M 747L; A-side Matrix # HS-1921-3 M-747-L A4RS-5240-1-D
        - Jackson, Michael - Music & me, 1973; SR-30768; Jackson, Michael (Box 316)
          Catalog # M 767L; A-side Matrix # 1309210-13A HS-2057-1
        - Jackson, Michael - Just another part of me; Rock with you (remixes), 2004; SR-30769; Jackson, Michael (Box 316)
          Catalog # SOX 1; A-side Matrix # SOX 1 A
        - Jackson, Michael - P.Y.T.; Dance ritual, 2003; SR-30770; Jackson, Michael; Drums Power (Box 316)
          Catalog # BRH009; A-side Matrix # BRH-009 A
          Ballroom Records
        - Janelle and The Cause - Try love, 1985; SR-30771; Janelle and The Cause (Box 316)
          Catalog # BAZ-101; A-side Matrix # BAZ-101-A S-14570
          Bazaar Records
        - John, Elton - Nobody wins, 1981; SR-30773; John, Elton (Box 316)
          Catalog # PRO-A-948; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-948-A1
        - Johnny P - Nasty man, 1989; SR-30774; Johnny P (Box 316)
          Catalog # VPRD 499; A-side Matrix # VPRD-449-A NASTY MAN
          Steely & Clevie Records
          Jamaica, New York
        - JT the Bigga Figga - Peep game; Game recognize, 1993; SR-30775; JT the Bigga Figga (Box 316)
          Catalog # GLR-002; A-side Matrix # S-28818 GLR-002A
          Get Low Recordz
        - Jackson, Michael - Bad, 1987; SR-30944; Jackson, Michael (Box 147)
          Catalog # 49 07462; A-side Matrix # XSS-174177-1A
        - Jacksons - Heartbreak hotel, 1980; SR-30945; Jacksons (Box 147)
          Catalog # AS 894; A-side Matrix # XSS-168051-IF
        - Jonzun Crew - Pack jam (look out for the OVC), 1982; SR-30946; Jonzun Crew (Box 147)
        - Juvet, Patrick - Lady night; Swiss kiss, 1979; SR-30947; Juvet, Patrick (Box 147)
          Catalog # NBD 20160 DJ; A-side Matrix # NBD-20160-AS-2CP